Alternate Dimension
Keep Out
Entrance
In our society,
a sedentary lifestyle...
stress...
and high-calorie foods are
everywhere you look.
These factors negatively impact
people's bodies on a daily basis.
Massage Relaxation
Beauty  Health  Diet
The Elf of the Forest
Hey, boss!
Tomoatsu Naoe
I finished organizing those files.
Thanks a bunch!
I've only got one more client
on the schedule for today,
Akiho Ino
so go ahead and- oh!
Can you wait an hour?
Wanna go out for drinks?
I'll pass.
Boo! You're no fun!
The boss tends to drink all night long,
and she gets handsy...
C'mon, have some!
Which isn't necessarily a bad thing, but...
Welcome to the-
I have an appointment.
My name is Elfuda.
Y-yes, ma'am!
Um...
M-my associate here will be helping you!
Huh? Me?!
Please, Naoe!
The client is creeping me out!
I'm Naoe.
Intake Form
Elfuda
Name
"Elfuda," eh?
That's a unique name.
Y'think so?
And you were interested in the Diet and
Bodywork Therapy program, correct?
Yes, that's right.
I'm in your hands now, human.
Emerald green eyes...
Maybe she's half Japanese?
Are there any specific areas
you're concerned about?
Lately, I've been feeling really insecure
about my love handles.
Same with my back...
Are... those her ears?
I was never this size
when I ran through the meadows...
I can't return to the forests of Kafar
looking like this...
The forests?
The forests of where?
Plus she's got big ears and
emerald green eyes...
lives in a strange forest,
and her name is Elfuda...
That's it! She's an ELF!
No, no! That can't be right...
Is something the matter?
M-my apologies!
Now, take off your jacket and
lie face down on the table for me.
Okay.
I ♥ GREASE
Y-you can leave your shirt on!
O-oh...
My bad. I'm new to this,
so I don't know how it works.
All good.
Then let's get started.
Everything alright?
Yup, A-OK!
It's my first time,
so it just startled me a little...
In that case, let's keep going.
Sh-should I lighten up on the pressure...?
Nah, dun worry!
I didn't feel a fing...
Pwease continue...
Massage Relaxation
Beauty  Health  Diet
I-I was so distracted by her reaction
that I kinda overdid it...
Wait, her ears-?!
You saw.
Uh, I-I saw nothing!
U-um, I swear it'll never leave this room!
No use hiding it now that I've been caught.
The truth is that I...
was an elf the whole time!
Behold my true form!
I'll grab a spare shirt for you,
so go ahead and get changed...
Oh, okay. Thanks.
Alternate Dimension
Keep Out
Entrance
So... you traveled here through
a portal from another dimension,
but you can't get home
'cause you gained weight.
Does that about sum it up?
Yes.
To traverse the portal that
connects your world to mine,
my weight must be the same
upon my return as it was when I left.
Makes sense...
By the way, why'd you come here?
Isn't it obvious?! I came here...
No way...
To invade us?!
...so that I could eat French fries!
That's the reason you-
Whaddya mean, "that's the reason"?!
You humans might not realize this,
but the so-called "food" in our world
is overwhelmingly primitive!
Our options are "roast" or "boil."
We basically eat raw ingredients.
Even seasonings like salt and pepper are
extremely rare, high-end luxury items!
Us elves happen to be vegetarians,
but there's hardly any variety
in our diets in the first place!
Now take someone like me and
give 'em human world flavors...
You deep-fry sliced potatoes in oil
and cover them with salt
like a shimmering layer of snow...
That crispy golden-brown crunch
is like heaven for my tongue!
French fries aren't junk food at all!
They're a blessing from the gods above!
That's why she's overweight...?
And they're insanely tasty,
so this happened...
In other words, this woman- er, elf-
is being inundated with foods
she never even knew existed.
That's why she eats in excess.
But then it dawned on me!
If I got fat 'cause of this world's food,
then I need this world's know-how
to get rid of it!
Human! As a resident of this world,
it's YOUR responsibility!
What?!
Wait, where were you hiding that bow?!
Thus began Elfuda's foray into
developing a healthier lifestyle.
Alright, time's up.
You did great today.
Whew, I'm beat...
I'm kinda hungry, so I'll have a few-
G-give me those!
French fries are off-limits
while you're on a diet!
We're aiming for a plant-based lifestyle!
But French fries are vegetables!
I'm vetoing your unfair rules!
Then how are you supposed to get home?!
We want a calorie deficit.
It's only for the duration of your diet,
so hang in there!
Gah!
Okay, fine!
It's that hard...?
We'll use dietary restrictions,
exercise, and osteopathy
to improve your physiological balance.
You'll see results so long as you
stick to the regimen.
What if I only eat French fries once a day?
Don't bargain with me...
Hello again!
You've been working hard lately.
Yes...
Swearing off French fries is more
miserable than I anticipated...
It'll be easier to burn fat once we
boost your metabolism a little.
Metabolism, eh?
In that case...!
Whoa! Look how big the tubs are!
Stays empty at this time of day.
Let's go get cleaned up and hop in!
No collecting firewood or drawing water...
This world is so convenient...
Half-body baths can help you
lose weight, too.
Oh, really?
And targeting your problem areas with
a massage while you're in the bath
doubles the effect!
Huh...
I'll take a nice hot tub
over a freezing river any day...
Ahh, that's the stuff!
I soaked in there for
a good thirty minutes...
I'm kinda thirsty, so I'll have a soda-
We drink water on a diet.
Aww...
One month later
Wow!
You look fantastic, Elfuda!
I didn't even recognize you!
Y-y'think so?
Well, it was all thanks to you, human.
I appreciate it.
You're the one who put in all the hard work.
Also, it's "Naoe."
Speaking of which, what's with the outfit?
These are normal clothes in my home world.
I see.
So does that mean you're
getting ready to leave?
Yeah. I can head back
through the portal now.
Thanks for all your help.
Take care of yourself!
Maybe I'll eat one last helping of
French fries before I hit the road...
Just make sure you don't overdo it again.
Right!
Elfuda went home with a smile on her face.
I doubt I'm ever going to see her again.
It makes me a little sad, but...
we literally live in different worlds.
I'm heading to lunch!
Okey-dokey!
It's been a while since I've eaten fast food.
I wonder how Elfuda's doing...
I know how much she likes French fries.
If she wanted, she could
make some at home.
But if she overeats and gains weight again-
What?! Elfuda?!
I thought you went home already!
I did.
Then what happened?
Whaddya mean? I came back.
You're under the impression that
interdimensional travel is hard...
Alternate Dimension
Keep Out
Entrance
But the portal itself is kinda like an
automatic door with a weight limit, y'know?
It's really not that big a deal.
Yeah, but... you went to
all the trouble of losing weight,
and now you're right back
where you started!
I learned something very important
from my most recent success:
Losing weight CAN be done!
Which means I get to eat as many
French fries as I want!
Because I can always
work off the weight again!
This woman- er, elf-
has only gotten worse...
So, on that note...
Huh?
...I'm in your hands once again, human.
It's "Naoe"...
In our society, a sedentary lifestyle...
stress, high-calorie foods, and...
Have a good one.
...otherworldly species are
everywhere you look.